cam18.com 2011-07-01

# Cam18.com - Privacy statement Cam18.com

In this privacy statement, Cam18.com explains which personal details it collects and uses and for what purpose.

**Information published by users**  
On this Website, users publish information by means of profiles, chat, webcam images and other resources. They are personally responsible for the personal details they include in that. Cam18.com can and will not check this in advance, but it will take action in the event of complaints.

You must take into consideration that information in your profile can be read by anyone, and that images made with the webcam and made available via the Website can be stored and shown elsewhere. Cam18.com has no control over this. For that reason, Cam18.com recommends you use a pseudonym and be cautious about publishing personal information.

Cam18.com does not store any copies of webcam recordings, apart from screenshots used on the homepage, or images used for promotion of the Website.

If you yourself include your personal details (such as e-mail address or telephone number) or other information you have submitted in your profile, or if you contact a user by bypassing this Website, Cam18.com cannot prevent the other user from tracing your name or contact details. Cam18.com does not check your profile for the presence of contact details.

**Processing by Cam18.com**  
Cam18.com stores and uses only those personal details that are submitted by you directly or of which it is clear that they are provided to us upon submittal. Details that are no longer needed are removed. You yourself also have the right to inspect, change or remove your details. Please contact Cam18.com.

Every time you use the Website, we register the pages you visit, which information you send and when, and how long (approximately) you visit the Website. If you are logged in, these visiting details are stored, linked to your username. Cam18.com stores all historical data of your visit(s) of the past 12 months. After that period they are automatically removed.

Cam18.com uses these details for statistical analyses of visiting and click behaviour on this website. These details are published or made available to third parties (such as advertisers) in aggregated form, but Cam18.com will do its utmost to ensure that none of the information in this aggregation can be traced back to you.

The Website also uses cookies to facilitate the logging on process for users. A cookie is a simple, small file that is sent along with pages of this Website, and which is stored on the hard disk of your computer by your browser. You can disable the use of cookies, although this may impair the functionality and ease of use of the website. However, Cam18.com does not use cookies to analyse your behaviour or to collect other privacy-sensitive details of you.

Cam18.com does not share your personal details with third parties, unless it is obliged to do so by law or if the competent authorities instruct Cam18.com to do so. In the event of identified abuse or suspected criminal offences, Cam18.com is entitled to forward all the information available on you to the competent authorities or - following legal intervention - to an aggrieved third party.

Cam18.com protects recorded personal details against unauthorised access and use. The files with user profiles and related details are password-protected for instance, and can only be retrieved and viewed by authorised personnel. However, this does not alter the fact that information can be viewed by the public as explained above.

**Your rights**  
You have the right to inspect, correct and change your personal details processed by us. The simplest way of doing this is via your management page. If you want to remove or correct other personal details, you must contact Cam18.com.

Messages in reviews, chats and profiles are in principle not removed but merely anonymised, unless there are serious reasons to remove them.

**Third-party websites**  
This privacy statement does not apply to websites of third parties hyperlinked to this website. Cam18.com cannot guarantee that these third parties handle your personal details in a reliable or safe manner, and we advise you to read the privacy statements of those websites before you use them.

**Changes to privacy statement**  
Cam18.com is entitled to change this privacy statement from time to time. We recommend consulting this statement on a regular basis, to keep yourself informed of any changes. Registered users are notified of changes in a timely fashion.
